poemslovers.com 2017-12-24

# Privacy Policy for PoemsLovers.com

The PoemsLovers.com has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site: [PoemsLovers.com](http://www.poemslovers.com/)

**Advertisers**  
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp). 

**Our Newsletter & opt-in and opt-out policies**  
If a visitor wishes to subscribe to our newsletter (containing the popular poems, stories and quotes), we ask for their e-mail address. In order to be subscribed to our Newsletter you must enter your information on a from on PoemsLovers.com and verify your subscription through an e-mail verification procedure. We have never purchased or sold e-mail addresses. Users who no longer wish to receive our newsletters may opt-out of receiving these communications by clicking the link at the BOTTOM of the e-mail you receive. You will be automatically removed. 

**Recommending a Poem, Quote, Story to a Friend.**  
When you recommend a poem or quote to a friend, we ask for both your email address and your friend's. We not share this information with third parties and we do not collect or use e-mail addresses of the senders or the recipients for any purposes. 

**Poetry, Stories, Quotes, Romantic Letters**  
On these sections of PoemsLovers.com the user is asked to submit his/her name and/or e-mail address. The information collected in these sections is not used in any way other than to identify the origin of the submission. In some cases, such as the Poetry and Stories sections, the user's e-mail address will be displayed along with their submission. 

**Automatically Generated E-mails.**  
In certain sections of the site, such as Poetry, Stories, Quotes, Newsletter and similar sections of PoemsLovers.com, users may receive an e-mail notification regarding their submission to the e-mail address the user specified when originating their submission. These computer-generated e-mails are used solely for the purpose of submission status notification. 

**IP Addresses**  
We collect and analyze traffic on our web site by keeping track of the IP addresses of our visitors. An IP address is a unique number assigned to your computer when you are browsing the internet. We log this information so that we can monitor overall traffic trends as well as the number of visitors visiting the web site. This information is used SOLELY to improve the quality of our web site. 

**Cookies**  
We use a technology nicknamed "cookies" on our web site. Cookies are pieces of information or data sent to your rowser from a web server and stored on your computer's hard drive for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies to make your visit to our web site easier. Cookies also allow us to count the number of unique and return visitors who use our site. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance their experience on our site. 

**Links**  
This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this web site. 

**Notification of Changes**  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. 

**Contacting the Web Site**  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact us: [Contact Us](http://www.poemslovers.com/contact_us.html)
